SEBASTIAN CURTIS LAVARIAS

WEB DEVELOPER

Mobile: 09972217704

E-mail: sebastiancurtislavarias@gmail.com

Web: https://bastilavarias.github.io Github: https://github.com/bastilavarias

Home Address:

406 Sta Fe St. Tondo Manila, Philippines

SUMMARY

I'm Sebastian Curtis Lavarias, 22 years old. I believe that great things can be done by a group of people through unity, trust, and teamwork. I make sure to follow through and finish the commitments that I have and I can adapt easily to different kinds of situations.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Vue.js / Sass
- PHP / Laravel / Node.js
- SOL
- Amazon Web Services
- Git

EDUCATION

Universidad De Manila

BS Information Technology 2018 - Present

Metropolitan Medical Center College of Arts Science & Technology

Senior Highschool 2016 - 2018

Tondo High School

Highschool 2012 - 2016

Magat Salamat Elementary School

Elementary 2006 - 2012

WORK EXPERIENCE

Outsourced Front-end Developer

<u>Vaskeappen</u> | Drøbak, Norway Nov 2021 - Present

Web Developer

Fourello | Philippines Dec 2020 - Present

WORK PROJECTS

Medgate

Medgate is a teleconsultation mobile app that allows patients to talk to doctors regarding various illnesses as well as receive follow-up care and virtual prescription. I was assigned to create and maintain the public website, web portal, and CSR chats part of the system.

- Role: Full-stack Web Developer
- Technologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

Inspire Church

Inspire App is designed to publish content and have the church members watch or listen to these contents. I was assigned to create and maintain the web portal part of the system.

- Role: Full-stack Web Developer
- Technologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

ZWELL Philippines

ZWELL Philippine Realty Development Corp is a Philippine-based real-estate corporation. I was assigned to create and maintain ZWELL's web portal.

- Role: Full-stack Web Developer
- Technologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

Vaskeappen

A mobile app that connects customers to self-employed cleaners with just a few taps of their fingers. I was assigned to create and maintain the public website and web portal part of the system.

- Role: Front-end Developer
- Technologies: JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS